The Amanda Steele Show.
Today's big up, big up goes to some scrawl Nigerian coffee
that probably fueled Tunde Onokoya,
a chess champ who decided to smash a Guinness Book World Record
by playing for 60 hours straight in the chaos of Times Square.
Just surviving Times Square for that long is a feat in itself,
like regardless of the chess games.
So I'm impressed about that.
You might actually know Tunde as the same guy who went viral
for simultaneously schooling like 12 other white chess folks
in a chess match.
I mean, he was just going one by one by one.
Gotcha, gotcha, gotcha.
Shut it down.
Check me, check me, check me.
His mission in breaking this world record
was to rake in a cool 1 million
for kids' education across Africa.
And guess what?
He hustled up 22,000 in just 22 hours.
So that's what I call making moves with a purpose.
Today's letdown goes to the fact
that I even have to talk about this foolishness,
a Chris Brown Quavo beef.
What even is that?
Some people are really hyping up the song,
but you know I'm Amanda.
So I'm not going to come at it
the same way everybody come at it
because sometimes I'm coming from a different angle
and this angle is really who cares?
I have a feeling this has to do
with like a text conversation or something,
which is so not gangsta at all.
And last but not least, I will just say this.
Quavo is still mourning the loss of his family.
I think he should be hands-off for at least five years.
You witnessed your best friend's murder.
And now R&B Cat is rapping at you about broads.
Let down.
We are, we are, we are.